logoorange.com 2018-10-19

# 

## Privacy policy

Logoorange is committed to protect and respect your privacy.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

## Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site our website, www.logoorange.com. We may also ask you for information if you report a problem with our Site;

if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence and your contact details;

details of your visits to our Site including, but not limited to, traffic data and other communication data.

## IP addresses and cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

We may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalised service.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you use our Site.

Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

## Where we store your personal data

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

to provide our Site and our services to you or deal with your enquiries;

to notify you about changes to our Site.

## Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

if we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about our customers or users will be one of the transferred assets;

if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.

## Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed logoorange1@gmail.com
